<resources>
    <string name="app_name">forties</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main4">Main4Activity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Book An Appointment</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Book a Health Center</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Health Blogs</string>

    <string name="home_second">Home Second</string>
    <string name="nephrology">Nephrology</string>

    <string name="title_activity_main5">Main5Activity</string>
    <string name="doc">Doctors</string>
    <string name="abt">About</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main6">Main6Activity</string>

    <string name="title_activity_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="avail">Available At</string>
    <string name="prof">Profile</string>

    <string name="title_activity_navigation">Navigation</string>
    <string name="blog1">Watch our expert, Dr.Ravi shankar, Hod....</string>
    <string name="dtl1"> We fight against corona virus (COVID-19)</string>
    <string name="blog2">Mask or no mask for COVID-19? Known For....</string>
    <string name="dtl2">Use of masks during the COVID-19 scare</string>
    <string name="terms">The copyright in all of the copyright works contained within these pages is either owned by Kable Intelligence Limited. or licensed to it. Reproduction of part or all of the contents of any of these pages is prohibited except to the extent permitted below.
                        These pages and the separate copyright works contained therein may be viewed on screen, downloaded onto a hard disk or printed for your personal use provided that you include this copyright notice on each copy and that you make no alterations to any of the pages and do not use any of the pages in any other work or publication in whatever medium stored. Copyright works contained in these pages may not be used, distributed or copied for any commercial purpose.
                        Without prejudice to the limited copyright licence granted above and solely to the extent that all or parts of these pages constitute a “database” for the purposes of the Copyright and Rights in Databases Regulations 1997 (“the Regulations”) reproduction of part or all of these pages is prohibited to the fullest extent permitted by the Regulations.</string>
    <string name="policy">
A premier private healthcare provider in Bangalore, Jyotsna Hospital established in 2020 with the goal of providing world-class medical service to the community.
The 120-bed, acute care, general medical/surgical private hospital has state-of-the-art facilities and an experienced team of healthcare professionals specialized in more than 30 medical and surgical specialties assuring comprehensive care. All physicians at jyotsna Hospital are Medical Board Certified or equivalent ensuring that patients receive international standard of care in India.</string>

    <string name="feedback"><a href="http://www.feedback.avriant.com/">Patient Feedback</a></string>

    <string name="title_activity_conference">Conference</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Chat</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Video</string>

</resources>
